And along with the IT sector, the
market will once again change its direction.
Before the results of tech, yesterday we saw
that the market was trading against the sector. There was a
good rally. Nifty leaders were
also included, but today's nervousness is
telling that there is a story, no story. Nervousness does happen
in investors' minds
before the results. And the way Infosys results were, some
clouds of crisis were
seen gathering over the sector. But
what are the expectations for the Czech results then? Will
these results be a little different? What will be special in this?
Our colleague
Anisha has joined to tell this. Anisha, tell me, did the Czech just
go on the path of Infosys or will it create some different
story? The
Street was already expecting very weak numbers for tomorrow's results
because
according to the guidance they gave for Impact 23, there could be a decline in the quarter,
almost 1.4% or the numbers will
remain flat and on a quarterly basis. So,
due to this, we are
expecting a slight decline for dollar revenue.  It
could be around ₹3220 million.
Revenue will be around ₹530 crore,
but margins will
decline by 140 basis points because of
seasonality. The pump segment is
very strong in Q3 and slows down in Q4.
Due to this, margins will be
flat. Profitability will also be less than 5%.
New Delhi New Deal wins may also
decline 5 to 10% on an average basis.
But going forward, it will be most important to
know the numbers in terms of guidance for Q5 24
from management, their country regarding
ramdowns, cancellations, and broadly slow rates. The
Street will be keeping a close eye on all these.
Estimates and guidance will be particularly watched.
But if we
talk about the overall charts, the stock definitely showed a rebound in yesterday's session
and today it is again
facing weakness.
How much support do you think this is
and will the stock weaken further from here for the future?
So I will avoid any IT
stock till the results are over
because the risk is there on the down side, what
we have seen is that there can be a fall of 10%
in stocks like Infosys also due to
expectations coming in after the results, so the
sentiment of the entire sector today is quite weak
on the last star, so I will
not keep a view on both, if there is a recovery post the results then we will
see, otherwise for now it is
better not to keep a view,
regarding tomorrow this share of Naresh is
down by 2.25% but we have told you